dnd-wiki.org 2012-12-19

# Dungeons and Dragons Wiki:Privacy policy - Dungeons and Dragons Wiki

A recent Firefox update is incompatible with our custom ratings extension: it won't display the text that you are typing in the box. So if you are using Firefox 17.0.1, you may need to manually add ratings for a while. There are no known problems with other browsers, however, so you could use one of those instead. 

From Dungeons and Dragons Wiki

Date of Last Revision: September 18, 2011 

This policy outlines the information Dungeons and Dragons Wiki collects, how we use that information, and how you can control how your information is shared. This policy applies only to Dungeons and Dragons Wiki (the “Site” or “Service”). Please be aware that when you follow a link to another site, this privacy policy does not apply, and Dungeons and Dragons Wiki has no control over what information they collect from you. Please further note that in the event that this policy conflicts with our terms of use, the terms of use controls. 

## [edit] The Information We Collect, And What We Do With It

In order to sign up for a Dungeons and Dragons Wiki account, only your username, password, and date of birth are required. An email address is also requested during sign-up. “Optional information” that we request you provide may include your first name, last name, and your gender. We may also request that you provide additional “optional information” such as your interests and hobbies for purposes of enhancing your profile among the Dungeons and Dragons Wiki community. Any “optional information” you choose to provide may be made public via your user page. We use this information to improve your experience with the Service, including the proper targeting of advertisements if any are displayed. 

Dungeons and Dragons Wiki also may send one or more cookies - a small file that lives in your web browser that helps the Service operate with full functionality (such as keeping you logged into the service). Most web browsers allow you to disable cookies, and you are welcome to continue to use the Service if you choose to do so. However, some of the Service’s features may not function properly if cookies are disabled. 

Dungeons and Dragons Wiki user data is stored in the United States, and its servers log some information whenever you access the Service; information such as your IP address, the time of your visit, your browser type and your browser's language setting. 

If you send a communication to the Company, we may hold onto that communication so that we can respond appropriately, and so that we can incorporate your feedback to improve the Service. 

You are not required to register for an account or to provide any personal information to us in order to use the Service. 

Dungeons and Dragons Wiki collects all the information you provide when you modify the content of a page or the Service (such as making edits, uploading images, etc.) An indicator that you provided that information is left on the History tab associated with the edited page or appropriate special/image page; on the Recent Changes link, and in your user contributions. 

## [edit] Sharing Your Information

Dungeons and Dragons Wiki only shares your information with others in the following circumstances: 

  * As described above 
  * As required by law enforcement agencies 
  * As Surgo, in his sole judgment, deems necessary to investigate a breach of security 

If the Service becomes involved in a merger or acquisition or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice to you, via an update to this policy, of any personal information to be transferred and/or subject to a different policy. 

We may also share with third parties aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of new user registrations over a specific time period or the number of users who edited a particular wiki. 

## [edit] Credit

Much of this text is credited to the [Wikia Central Privacy Policy](http://www.wikia.com/Privacy_Policy). Portions of that text which do not apply have been rewritten or purged for the purposes of this wiki.
